const data = [
  {
    id: 0,
    question: 'Who is the main character in the anime "Naruto"?',
    points: 0,
    options: {
      a: "Naruto",
      b: "Sasuke",
      c: "Ash",
      d: "Sakura",
    },
    correct: 1,
  },
  {
    id: 1,
    question: 'What is the name of the pirate crew in the anime "One Piece"?',
    points: 0,
    options: {
      a: "Blackbeard Pirates",
      b: "Straw Hat Pirates",
      c: "Marines",
      d: "Red Hair Pirates",
    },
    correct: 2,
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    question: 'In "Attack on Titan," what are the giant humanoid creatures that threaten humanity called?',
    points: 0,
    options: {
      a: "Humans",
      b: "Giants",
      c: "Titans",
      d: "Colossi",
    },
    correct: 3,
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    question: 'Who is the protagonist in "Fullmetal Alchemist" and what is his brother\'s name?',
    points: 0,
    options: {
      a: "Edward and Alphonse",
      b: "Roy and Riza",
      c: "Gon and Killua",
      d: "Naruto and Sasuke",
    },
    correct: 1,
  },
  {
    id: 4,
    question: 'What is the name of the virtual reality MMORPG in the anime "Sword Art Online"?',
    points: 0,
    options: {
      a: "Gun Gale Online",
      b: "Alfheim Online",
      c: "The World",
      d: "Aincrad",
    },
    correct: 4,
  },
  {
    id: 5,
    question: 'In "My Hero Academia," what is the Quirk of the protagonist, Izuku Midoriya?',
    points: 0,
    options: {
      a: "Fire Quirk",
      b: "Super Speed",
      c: "One For All",
      d: "Telekinesis",
    },
    correct: 3,
  },
  {
    id: 6,
    question: 'Which anime is set in a post-apocalyptic world and follows a boy and his dog?',
    points: 0,
    options: {
      a: "Neon Genesis Evangelion",
      b: "Cowboy Bebop",
      c: "Trigun",
      d: "Akira",
    },
    correct: 3,
  },
  {
    id: 7,
    question: 'What is the name of the sorcerer guild in "Fairy Tail"?',
    points: 0,
    options: {
      a: "Mage Alliance",
      b: "Dark Guild",
      c: "Black Clover",
      d: "Fairy Tail",
    },
    correct: 4,
  },
  {
    id: 8,
    question: 'In "Death Note," what is the name of the genius high school student who finds the Death Note?',
    points: 0,
    options: {
      a: "Ryuk",
      b: "Kira",
      c: "Light Yagami",
      d: "L",
    },
    correct: 3,
  },
  {
    id: 9,
    question: 'Which anime features a group of students who form a club to save their school\'s culture, known as the SOS Brigade?',
    points: 0,
    options: {
      a: "Clannad",
      b: "K-On!",
      c: "The Melancholy of Haruhi Suzumiya",
      d: "Nichijou",
    },
    correct: 3,
  },
];

export default data;
